你好，你这个漂亮的人。
HELLO YOU BEAUTIFUL PERSON.
井。
Well.
嗯，你现在一定为自己感到无比自豪。
Well you must be feeling super proud of yourself right now right.
你在课程的这一部分已经走到了这一步，所以为了充分庆祝我想要制作一段视频
You've come so far in this section of the course so to fully celebrate that I wanted to make a video
快速回顾一下，这样您就可以沉浸在您在
and have a quick recap so that you can soak in all the awesome stuff you've learned in the section of
这门课。
the course.
因此，您从非常基础的开始，学习了如何使用图形打开和关闭航站楼
So you started off with the very basics and you learned how to open and close the terminal using graphical
方法，并使用现在广受欢迎的键盘快捷键。
methods and by using And now beloved keyboard shortcuts.
一开始对你来说很陌生，但你还是直接跳了进来，开始打字
And it was all very strange to you at first but you jumped right in anyway and you started typing and
使用第一个命令，您可以看到DATE命令、CAL命令和ECHO命令。
using your first commands you saw the date command the Cal command and the echo command.
你看到了如何清除你的学期历史。
And you saw how to clear your term history.
我们毕竟不想让任何间谍看历史，我们也不想。
We don't want any spies looking at history after all do we.
他们，我们正在取得进展，但这一切都有些奇怪，你可能不太确定是什么
They we're making progress but it was all kind of weird and you probably weren't too sure of what was
当您运行命令时，实际上正在运行。
actually going on when you run a command.
然后，您了解了终端和外壳之间的区别。
So then you learned the difference between the terminal and the shell.
您了解到shell解释您键入的命令，就像解释
You learned that the shell is what interprets the commands that you type just like you interpret the
你所读单词的含义。
meanings of words that you read.
当你理解了什么是实际的命令时，你就了解了命令的一般结构。
And when you understood what commands actually were you learned the general structure of a command.
了解了命令遵循命令名选项参数结构。
Learned the commands follow a command name options arguments structure.
好的。
OK.
现在，因为很明显，尽管命令遵循相似的结构，但它们确实有很大的不同
Now because it became clear that although commands follow a similar structure they do vary quite a bit
在他们的使用中。
in their usage.
他们每个人都有自己特定的选项和用例，要记住它们是不可能的
They each have their own specific options and use cases and it would be impossible to memorize them
全。
all.
因此，您学习了如何查看Linux手册，了解了手册是如何分解的，您可以看到
So you learned how to look in the Linux manual you learned how the manual was broken up and you saw
如何搜索术语和阅读手册页面，以及如何自己学习新事物和查找
how to search for terms and read the manual pages and how to learn new things for yourself and find
事情在你需要的时候就去做，而不是必须记住所有的事情。
things as and when you need them rather than having to memorize everything.
这就像在你的电脑上有你自己的个人搜索引擎，这是相当令人难以置信的
So it's like having your own personal search engine for your computer which is pretty incredible in
这是我的意见。
my opinion.
现在，我们更深入地讨论，您了解到命令可以将输入作为标准
Now then we took our discussion even deeper and you learned that commands can take input a standard
输入和命令行参数，它们可以通过标准输出和标准错误数据获得输出
input and command line arguments and they can get output via standard output and standard error data
溪流。
streams.
因此，我必须将这些数据流重定向到您希望的任何位置，以及如何将不同的命令连接在一起
So I had to redirect these data streams to wherever you wish and how to pipe together different commands
建造强大的管道。
to build powerful pipelines.
我希望使用T命令和X Ogg命令来获得额外的管道灵活性。
I hope to use the T command and the X Ogg's command for extra pipeline flexibility.
你在这么短的时间内走了这么远，这真的很令人惊讶。
And this really is amazing how far you've come in such a short amount of time.
所以我想制作这个视频来祝贺你到目前为止取得的进步，你做得很好，你这台小电脑
So I want to make this video to congratulate you on your progress so far so well done you little computer
天才您现在在下一节中，您将学习如何导航Linux文件系统和
genius you now in the next section you're going to learn about navigating the Linux file system and
您还将学习一些在管道中使用的新构建块。
you'll also learn some new building blocks to use in your pipelines.
但在此之前，我有一个项目要给你完成，这个项目将挑战你建造你的
But before that I have a project for you to complete the project will challenge you to build your very
拥有Linux命令管道。
own Linux command pipeline.
现在它将会很棒，它将作为荣誉的徽章，因为你已经学到了所有的东西
Now it's going to be awesome and it will serve as a badge of honor that you have learned everything
我们已经在这一节讲到了这些，这样你们就可以有信心在下一个视频中继续下去了，我是
that we've covered in this section so that you can feel confident moving on now in the next video I'm
我会给你你的项目摘要。
going to be giving you your project brief.
再次祝贺你做得令人惊叹。
So congratulations once again you're doing amazingly.
我们在那里见。
And I'll see you there.